How lonely are you?
你有多孤独？
Sometimes living alone or being in a remote location with nobody around to talk to can give you the feeling of despair and isolation.
有时独自生活或身处偏远之地，周围无人交谈，会让你产生绝望和孤独的感觉。
It's not a great feeling.
这不是一种好的感觉。
There's a common stereotype that it's something that affects older people more, but research has found that loneliness is something that can affect us all, whatever our age.
人们普遍存在一种刻板印象，认为孤独更多地影响老年人，但研究发现，无论年龄大小，孤独都可能影响我们所有人。
There's a familiar phrase that says it's possible to be lonely in a crowd – despite being surrounded by hundreds of people, you think you have nobody to talk to or to connect with and that nobody wants to listen to you anyway.
有一个常见的说法：“人群中也可能感到孤独”——尽管被许多人包围，你却觉得无人可谈、无人可联系，甚至认为没人愿意听你说话。
It's probably not true, but loneliness is seen as a big problem for the mental health of the population wherever they live - so much so that the British government even has a minister for loneliness.
这或许并非事实，但无论人们住在哪里，孤独都被视为心理健康的一大问题——英国政府甚至为此设立了“孤独事务大臣”。
The BBC recently completed a survey about the topic and it found that people aged between 16 and 24 experience loneliness more often and more intensely than any other age group.
BBC最近完成了一项关于该主题的调查，发现16至24岁的人群比其他任何年龄组更频繁、更强烈地体验孤独。
Researchers from the University of Manchester who analysed the data, suggested feeling lonely may plague the young because it's a time of identity change - figuring out your place in the world and of learning to regulate emotions.
曼彻斯特大学分析数据的研究人员指出，孤独可能困扰年轻人，因为这是身份转变的时期——确定自己在世界中的位置和学习调节情绪。
Psychology lecturer and BBC presenter Claudia Hammond says that "it's tempting to conclude that something about modern life is putting young people at a higher risk of loneliness, but when we asked older people in our survey about the loneliest times in their lives, they also said it was when they were young."
心理学讲师兼BBC主持人克劳迪娅・哈蒙德表示：“人们很容易得出结论，认为现代生活的某些因素让年轻人面临更高的孤独风险，但当我们在调查中询问老年人一生中最孤独的时期时，他们也说是年轻时。”
The issue is certainly being talked about more.
人们现在确实更频繁地讨论这个问题。
And in the UK, the Minister for Loneliness Tracey Crouch has said that "the government now recognises loneliness as one of the biggest health challenges we face."
英国孤独事务大臣特蕾西・克劳奇表示：“政府现在认识到，孤独是我们面临的最大健康挑战之一。”
She also said there needs to be a "national conversation" to end the stigma about admitting to feeling lonely.
她还称需要进行“全国性对话”，以消除承认孤独感的羞耻感。
The BBC Loneliness Experiment also found the type of culture you live in has implications for loneliness.
BBC“孤独实验”还发现，你所处的文化类型也对孤独有影响。
People from cultures which tend to put a high value on independence, such as Northern Europe and the US, revealed they would be less likely to tell a colleague about their loneliness.
来自北欧和美国等重视独立文化的人表明，他们不太可能向同事倾诉孤独。
But in cultures where extended family is often emphasised, such as in Southern Europe, Latin America, Asia and Africa, older women in particular were at lower risk of feeling lonely.
但在南欧、拉丁美洲、亚洲和非洲等强调大家庭的文化中，老年女性尤其较少感到孤独。